Narrator: 9A
Speaker: a living room
the box office
traffic
noise
jacket
hear
darling
half an hour
towards
outside
Are you sure?
Have a good day.
See you in 20 minutes.
Narrator: 9B
Speaker: a private investigator
a case
a colleague
a client
work experience
sit at a desk
answer phone calls
investigate a problem
follow
stay awake
solve a case
missing
boring
satisfying
Narrator: 10A
Speaker: a tourist destination
the coast
an island
a lake
a castle
a visitor
a bar
a day trip
a boat trip
a monster
a room for tonight
a great view
on the second floor
Enjoy your stay.
Narrator: 10B
Speaker: a robbery
a bank
a suspect
a detective
yesterday
yesterday afternoon
last night
last Friday night
secret
strong
together
the 15th century
lock
store rooms
a building
a luxury hotel